### Enzo Vezzaro

### UI / UX designer and Web developer



enzovezzaro05@gmail.com





Pavia, Italy Open to move



enzovezzaro.com insuladigitalstudio.com





github.com/EnzoVezzaro



Hello, I'm Enzo. I love being creative, exploring and broadening my horizons, create high quality product and giving stunning user experience to my products. I'm an enthusiast of user interface, experience design, and clean and usable coding.

## Experiences

May 2017 - Present

Junior Front-End Developer, UI Designer Eleva.it

Pavia, Italy

January 2016 - Present

Head Developer / Art Director Vapecloudshop.com

Santo Domingo, RD

August 2015 - January 2016

Head Developer Thevapelifestore.com

Hollywood, CA

September 2014 - Present

**CEO** 

InsulaDigitalStudio.com

Creating Web/Native Expiriences with modern web technoligies.

### **Education**

2017 - 2018

Google Developer Challenge Scholarship: Mobile Web

Worldwide

2012 -

Computer Science Degree (in process)

Los Angeles City College

Los Angeles, California

2006 - 2010

Multimedia and Communication Diploma

I.P.S. Americo D'Aschio

Vicenza, Italy

# Languages

Spanish: Native Italian: Native

#### Tools

Mac OS X Atom Sketch Adobe Suite Affinity Suite Slack Trello InVision Git

### Design Skills

Photography Prototype design Web design Responsive design App Design



# **Development Skills**

SASS, JADE, Gulp, Foundation, Bootstrap Javascript, ¡Query, Firebase, Netlify, Moltin, Git, CLI, And now, pretty intrigue by the React (Native) world. Loading ...

#### Hobies













